行了 Eileen 我来吧
It's okay, eileen. I got this.
- 你确定?abc- 是的 你回家吧
- Are you sure?abc- Yeah. You get home.
谢了 Danny 明早见
Thanks, danny. See you in the morning.
到时见
I'll be here.
食物派完了 Daryl 我们关门了
Food's gone, daryl. We're closed.
你这儿有没有多余的外套?
You wouldn't happen to haveabcan extra coat in there, would you?
- 你不穿正着外套嘛abc- 我要一件冬衣 伙计 外头很冷
- You're wearing a coat.abc- A winter coat, man. It's cold.
来吧
Come on.
给你
Here.
骑警队?(纽约的冰球队)abc你让我在新泽西穿这个?
Rangers? You expectabcme to wear this in jersey?
拜托 伙计 你开什么玩笑?
Come on, man,where'sabcyour sense of humor?
晚安 Daryl
Good night, daryl.
走开
Go away.
一点也不好笑 变态
That's not funny, freak.
没人在开玩笑 Daniel
No one is laughing,daniel.
星期五有事吗?
You doing anything friday?
带一位可爱的年轻女士去听交响乐
Taking a lovely youngabclady to the philharmonic.
就是说你要找一个妓女上床?
That your way of saying you'reabchaving sex with a hooker?
两个 一个奏不出和声
Two. Can't create aabcharmonic with just one.
我原本想你抽空参加abcRachel的闪赫芭芝礼 这是一个...
Well, I was hoping you might availableabcfor rachel's simchat bat. It's A...
婴儿命名礼 传统犹太仪式abc源自20世纪60年代
jewish baby-naming ceremony, a time-honoredabctradition dating all the way back to the 1960s.
7点 在我家
My house at 7:00.
只有拉比(犹太教学者)abc和几个朋友 家人
It'll just be the rabbi andabca few friends and some family.
用繁缛礼节庆贺婴儿降生虚伪透顶
Nothing like welcoming a baby into the worldabcwith a completely naked display of hypocrisy.
会有很多酒 还有很多老好人abc让你在暗地里嘲笑
There'll be plenty of wine andabcnice people you can quietly mock.
我也想去 但我已经abc预定了16箱果子露酒
Wish I could, but I already put downabca deposit on 16 crates of jell-O.
House...
一晚而已 我希望你能来
it's one evening. I'dabclike you to be there.
唠唠叨叨的布道 用海绵擦身
Religious hokum, get sponge bath.
我能不能考虑一下?
Can I get back to you?
需要帮忙吗?
Can I help you?
随便看看 谢了
Just browsing. Thanks.
又被打入冷宫了高兴吗?
Happy to be underachieving again?
管理急诊室简直是懒人的美差
Running the E.R.Is slacker heaven.
你想找什么?
Looking for anything in particular?
不用找了 这家伙在哪?
Not anymore. Where's this guy?
- 找他干嘛?abc- 因为他是我下一个病人
- Why?abc- 'Cause he's my next patient.
不作自我介绍就太没礼貌了
It'd be rude of me notabcto introduce myself.
他不过是个喝醉了酒abc幻想见到耶稣的牧师
He's a drunk priestabcwho hallucinated jesus.
害怕自己漏掉了什么?
Afraid you might have missed something?
害怕你浪费大家时间
Afraid you're everyone's time?
很明显 不是酒精便是疲劳引致
It's obviously eitherabcalcohol or exhaustion.
就是说 你搞不清是哪个?
So you admit you have no idea which?
我承认 我没时间关心你在和谁捣乱
I admit that I'm too busy toabccare who you're screwing with.
不用谢 能帮上点忙就让我很欣慰了
Don't thank me. Just knowing I canabcbe of assistance is thanks enough.
你折腾半天就选了他?
you went out of your way to pick him?
- 什么问题也没有abc- 医者无小病
- This is nothing.abc- There are no small cases.
不猜猜我唱的哪一出?
Any guesses where this joke is going?
- 可能是精神运动性癫痫abc- 可能只是醉酒
- Could be psychomotor epilepsy...abc- could be alcohol.
是不是应该先让急诊室abc排除明显的病因--
Shouldn't we let theabcE.R.Rule the obvious out--
可能是阿托品中毒 枕叶肿瘤
could be atropine toxicity,abcoccipital lobe tumor.
你是不是知道什么瞒着我们?
You know something about thisabccase you're not telling us?
为什么要这么想?
Why would you think that?
因为你想耍我们
'Cause you want to screw with us.
或者耍一个有幻觉的牧师
Or screw with a hallucinating priest.
两者皆有可能abc找出答案最好的方法是
Both are possible. There'sabconly oneay to find out.
去做个脑电图检查癫痫abc做个CT扫描肿瘤
Run an E.E.G.For epilepsy.abcC.T. His brain for tumors.
还有去他的教堂搜查有毒物质
And go check his houseabcof god for toxins.
14 等等
Fourteen, hold up.
这部门人心散了 除非回复正常abc否则我不会接真正的病例
This department is broken, and I'm notabcgonna take a real case until it's fixed.
工作还是恋爱-- 你们选
Job or relationship--abcyour choice.
什么?
What?
换个说法可能好懂点abc要么分手 要么辞职
To put iin terms you might betterabcunderstand, if you don't split, you must quit.
药物实验告一段落了abc我退出了 她也退出了
The drug trial isabcover. M out, she's out.
我不管
Don't care.
我们是成年人了 能兼顾得来abc你至少要给我们个机会
We're adults. We can handle this.abcYou just have to give us a chance.
不 你们不是 你们不能 我不给
No, you're not. No, youabccan'T. And no, I don'T.
好好考虑下 在这假病例结束前给我答复
Mull it over. You got until theabcend of this fake case to decide.
我没醉
I wasn't drunk.
我只喝了一两杯
I had one or two drinks.
人们往往会低估酒精的作用--
People often underestimateabcalcohol's effect on their--
正准备喝第六杯 我清楚酒精的影响abc这不是酒精的问题
I was on my way to six. I know how alcoholabcaffects me. This wasn't the alcohol.
你在曼哈顿住了3年
you lived in manhattan r three years.
然后在俄勒冈1年 新墨西哥18个月abc在威斯康辛州不到1年
Then a year in oregon, 18 months in newabcmexico, less than a year in wisconsin,
近6个月才搬到特伦顿?abc(新泽西州首府)
and now you've been living inabctrenton for the last six months.
是的
Yep.
我们对你了解的越多abc就更容易治疗疾病
The more we know about you, theabcmore likely it is we can help you.
嗯 这和医学无关 所以--
Mm, it's not medicallyabcrelevant, so--
除非你上过医学院abc你可不知道什么有关
no way to know unless youabcwent to medical school.
4年前 教堂青年会有个十来岁abc的孩子告我对他有不当接触
Four years ago, a teen in a youth group atabcmy church accused me of inappropriate contact.
我是无辜的 但教堂决定把我调走
I was innocent, but theabcchurch decided to transfer me.
说这样对全部当事人都有好处
Said it would be easierfor all involved.
当新教区的居民得知abc我被调走的原因后
When the parishioners at the new churchabcgot wind of why I'd been transferred,
他们很不满
they were unhappy.
所以我一直被调来调去abc这和医学有什么关系?
I was sent off again and again, andabchow is any of that medically relevant?
就是说那孩子撒谎?
So the kid lied?
他误会了
He was confused.
误会你性骚扰他?
Confused whether you molested him or not?
够了 你问我为什么搬来搬去abc我告诉你了
Okay, you wanted to know why Iabcmoved around so much,and I told you.
该你告诉我为什么会产生幻觉了
How about telling me whyabcI was hallucinating?
梅毒可以解释幻觉
Syphilis could explain the hallucination.
我没有性行为
I'm not sexually active.
你不必坦白对那个孩子做过什么abc你又不是生来就是牧师
You don't have to admit you did anything withabcthe kid. You weren't always a priest.
我从12岁起就想成为牧师abc17岁进了神学院
I wanted to be since I was 12. Iabcentered the seminary when I was 17.
也许那不是幻觉abc也许真的是基督降临
Maybe it wasn't a hallucination.abcMaybe it really was jesus.
我没有发疯
I'm not insane.
看见基督代表你发疯了?
seeing jesus makes you insane?
这似乎不是一个牧师应有的虔诚态度
A bit of an oddabcattitude coming from a priest.
只是一份工作罢了abc我早就没有了对神迹的向往
Well, it's just a job now. Theabcfairy tale ended a long time ago.
你是胆小鬼 娘娘腔
You're a wuss--partabcwimp, part puss.
我别无选择 我是仪式的一部分
I have no choice. I'mabcpart of the ceremony.
我以为你割过包皮了
I thought you were already circumcised.
只是为了朋友 去呆上一晚
It's one night for a friend.
要是你另一个朋友手上有两张abc"Brubeck的蓝调"音乐会票子 如何?
What about the friend who has twoabctickets to see brubeck at the blue note?
- 我还以为你要去花天酒地abc- 我撒谎了
- I thought you had an orgy planned.abc- I lied.
你有两张Brubeck的票 也是撒谎?
Are you lying about the brubeck tickets?
没错 想搭救你一下
Yes, but only to save you from yourself.
如果你不出现 我和Cuddy都没意见
I'll be fine and so willabcCuddy if you don't show up.
我甚至很讶异她邀请了你
I'm surprised she even invited you.
这也算是一种奉承了
It is oddly flattering.
上帝 我受够了他的无理取闹
God, I'm so sick of his stupid stunts.
所有人都要忍受自己老板的无理取闹
Everybody has to put up withabctheir boss's stupid stunts.
不 我们不必
No, they don't.
我们有人事部 有Cuddyabc还有别的工作
There's H.R. There'reabcCuddy. There's other jobs.
House才不听人事部的
House doesn't listen to H.R.
没等Cuddy炒他 他就把我们炒了abc而且我不想找别的工作
Cuddy will let him fire us before sheabcfires him, and I don't want another job.
你为什么粘着他?abc你为什么要替他说话?
Why do you cling thim?abcWhy do you defend him?
我不想失业 但不代表我离不开他
Just because I don't want to beabcunemployed doesn't mean I'm codependent.
我没说你离不开他abc我只是说你害怕了
I'm not saying you're codependent.abcI'm saying you're scared.
你知道吗?
You know what?
你说得对
You're right.
你想辞职?
So you want to quit?
不 我要阻止他无理取闹
No, I want to stop a stupid stunt.
House不想我们任何一个辞职abc他要的是
House doesn't want either oneabcof us to quit. He wants this.
把两只小白鼠放进迷宫abc扔下一块芝士让它们抢
He's got two lab rats in a mazeabcand thrown in one piece of cheese.
那-- 我们怎么做?
S--so whatabcdo we do?
什么也不做
Nothing.
- 酷abc- 因为他性骚扰小孩?
- cool.abc- It's cool he's a child molester?
因为他是一个不信上帝的牧师
It's cool the priest doesn'tabcbelieve in god.
酷 因为他怎么对那孩子abc上帝就怎么对他
It's cool that god did toabchim what he did to the kid.
还没证实
Allegedly.
- 你认为他是无辜的?abc- 他有双诚实的眼睛?
- You think he's innocent?abc- He had honest eyes?
而你认为他有罪abc所以死活要把他赶出院
And you think he's guilty, which explainsabcwhy you're dying to discharge him.
我让他出院是因为他没病abc不是因为他有恋童癖
I'm dying to discharge him because he'sabcnot sick, not because he's a pedophile.
还没证实
Allegedly.
你真相信是那个孩子误会了?
You actually believe theabckid got confused?
如果所有人都撒谎abc那也包括十来岁的男孩
If everybody lies,thatabcincludes teenage boys.
有这么个好玩的病人abc我们真走运
aren't we luck to haveabcsuch an interesting patient?
不再是了-- 他什么毛病也没有
Had--there's nothingabcwrong with him.
世上最无聊的病历变成了悬疑小说
The world's most boring caseabcjust became a page turner.
你却要把它的结局撕掉?
You want to tear out the last chapter?
你想了解他的人品 去施粥处问好了
You want to examine hisabccharacter, go to a soup kitchen.
我们不会再测试捏造出的病了
We are done testing him forabcthings he doesn't have.
对Foreman和13来说是个坏消息
Bad news for Foreman and thirteen.
- 病例结束了abc- 我们不打算分手
- case is over.abc- We're not splitting up.
那你们哪位打算走人?
So which one of you is taking a hike?
我们也不打算辞职
And neither of us is quitting.
有意思
Interesting.
既然你不介意Chase和Cameron约会
You were fine with chaseabcand cameron dating.
- 显然你没这方面的问题--abc- 你被开除了
- You obviously don't actuallyabchave an issue-- - you're fired.
你到底想玩到什么时候?abc我们知道你不会--
How long are you gonna keepabcthis up? We know you're not--
你又错了
wrong... again.
最近几周 我几乎不记得abc你作过任何正确的诊断
In fact, in the last few weeks, it'sabchard to remember a correct call you made.
如果Chase当年为了帮Cameronabc影响他的专业判断 我也会炒他
If chase had compromised his professional judgmentabcto help cameron,I'd have fired his ass, too.
换药的事败露以后abc你想方设法阻止我联系制药公司
When my mistake blew up, you did everythingabcto keep me from contacting the drug company.
我想保住你的执照而不是饭碗abc更不是你的恋情
To save your lense,not your jobabcand definitely not your relationship.
好了 证件
So, badge.
好
Fine.
你何不去给我们abc找个真正的病例?
Why don't you see if youabccan find us a real case?
你们不知我出了什么问题abc怎么能让我出院?
How can you discharge me when youabchave no idea what's wrong?
我们知道是什么问题abc你一觉睡醒就没事了...
We know what's wrong, andabcnow that you've slept it off...
不只是幻觉
It's not just a hallucination.
我还觉得恶心
I feel nauseous.
脚发麻 像僵了一样
My foot feels numbabclike it's fallen asleep.
你之前没提过
You didn't mention that before.
我之前没发现
I didn't notice it before.
你是不是想逃避某个人?
Are you hiding from someone?
为什么这么想留在这里?
Why are you so intent on staying here?
我感觉很糟糕abc我知道身上有不妥
I don't feel well. I knowabcthere's something wrong with me.
哪只脚?
Which foot?
左脚
My left.
噢 上帝
Oh, god.
这是什么? 什么东西?
What the hell is that? What is that?
你的脚趾掉了
Your toe just fell off.
今天一定是我的幸运日
Must be my lucky day.
出现新症状意味着旧症状属实abc我们的鸡奸犯牧师可以留下了
New symptom means the dsymptom was a real symptom,abcand I get to keep our pederast priest after all.
Foreman和13去哪了?
Where are Foreman and thirteen?
他们走了
They left.
麻疯病会导致坏疽和幻觉
Leprosy can causeabcnecrosis and hallucination.
他们为什么要走?
Why would they leave?
因为Foreman不在这里工作了abc而13恼火我开除了他
Because Foreman doesn't work here anymore,abcand thirteen is mad that I fired him.
别担心 她会回来的abc她发发脾气以表明立场
Don't worry. She'll be back. She'll beabcpissed off. She'll want to take a stand.
但Foreman会劝她说abc不能两个人都失业
And then Foreman will convince her that there'sabcno reason both of them should be out of a job.
麻疯病不大符合
Leprosy's a bad fit.
为什么要开除Foreman?
Why'd you fire Foreman?
我让他选-- 分手还是走人
I gave him a choice--abcsplit or quit.
他都不选
He chose neither.
麦角中毒如何?
What about ergotism?
他为她放弃职业生涯?
He's giving up his career for her?
他为她放弃这份工作
He's giving up this career for her.
不对 白血球数正常
No, normal white blood count.
一氧化碳中毒?
Carbon monoxide poisoning?
他们是好医生
They're good doctors.
分开来看 他们很棒 比你们好
Separately,they're greatabcdoctors, better than you.
放在一起 他们是白痴
Together, they're morons.
去搜他的房子 当真病例那样搜
Go check out the house that theyabcwould've checked had this been a real case.
去呼13 让她检查血液里有没一氧化碳
And page thirteen. Tell herabcto run the blood for c-O.
让那牧师去高压氧舱呆着abc以防再有别的部分掉下来
And get the priest in a hyperbaricabcchamber before anything else falls off.
我们该怎么办?
So what are we gonna do now?
我去问Cuddy要推荐信abc去找份新的工作
I get a letter of recommendationabcfrom Cuddy an find a new job.
就这样? 你放弃了?
Oh, that's it? You're jus gonna give up?
House说得对
House is right.
我们的关系影响了我的判断
Our relationship did affect my judgment.
我应该辞职
Then I should quit.
我另找一份工作更容易
It'll be easier forabcme to find another job.
但不像这份这样
Not like this one.
我们应该一起辞职
We should both quit.
这有什么用呢?
What's that gonna accomplish?
别担心
Don't worry.
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
我们都会没事的
We'll be fine.
去吧
Go ahead.
- 今晚见?abc- 我早点回家
- I'll see you tonight?abc- I'll be home early.
你真觉得House放弃了Foreman?
you really think houseabcis done with Foreman?
问我的话 我觉得Foreman早晚会放弃13
if you ask me, Foreman shouldabcbe done with thirteen.
他找不到好工作 到头来会责怪她abc连累他失业
He's not gonna get a better job, which meansabche'll end up resenting her for losing this one,
她也会因此怨恨他
which she'll end up resenting.
或者艰难的境况abc会让他们靠得更近
Or the hardship'llabcbring 'em closer together.
没准会邀几个女伴和Foreman分享
She'll invite friendsabcover for Foreman to share.
暖炉没有泄漏
No leaks in the heater.
她不是色情狂
she's not a nympho.
她是双性恋abc她习惯了无需指引就能找到宝藏的爱人
She's bisexual,which, by the way, means she'accustomedabcto partners who don't need a map to find the treasure.
一氧化碳可能来自香烟
C-o poisoning might haveabccome from these cigarettes.
除非他在玻璃罩里面吸
Not unless he wasabcsmoking them in a bell jar.
即使知道宝藏在哪abc没铲子还是挖不到
And even if you know where the treasure is, it canabcstill be pretty hard to dig it up without a shovel.
铲子可以买
You can buy a shovel.
让我想想...
Let's see...
怎样才能阻止House去破坏abc我那虚伪的传统仪式呢?
how do I keep house from ruining myabcprecious display of religious hypocrisy?
有了 强迫他参加
I know, I'll pressure him to attend,
因为他不会做任何abc我指望他做的事
knowing that he'll never agree toabcanythingI actually want him to do.
我没强迫你 我只是邀请你
I didn't pressure you. I invited you.
再说尊重自己的宗教传统和虚伪无关
And there's nothing hypocriticalabcabout recognizing your heritage.
那你依犹太食谱吃饭 披四角巾abc屠宰小牛献祭了么?
So you keeping kosher now, wearingabcfour-cornered garments, slaughtering heifers to the god ra?
慢 这不是你们的传统么?
Wait, is that one your people?
要么做全套 要么一件不做abc还有C选项-- 你是骗子和伪君子
Do it all, do nothing,or optionabc"c"-- you're a liar and a hypocrite.
House...
不管好坏 你都是我生命的一部分
for better or for worse,youabcare a part of my life.
这不是什么手段abc我发自内心地邀请你
It isn't a ploy. It'sabca sincere invitation.
我真的希望你能来
I honestly want you to come.
我无论如何也不会错过
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
你这白痴
You idiot.
我正要松口气
I was free and clear.
现在他要来了 都是你的错
Now he's coming,and it's your fault.
从何时起 你用谎言策略一流产abc就变成了我的错?
Since when have your failed attempts atabccommunication through lies become my fault?
从你管不住嘴巴开始
Since you forgot how toabckeep your mouth shut.
你把事情搞砸了 你得负责搞定
You messed it up, andabcnow you're gonna fix it.
别告诉他是我指使的
And you're gonna keep my name out of it.
他怎么样了?
how is he?
很稳定 坏疽看来没有扩散
Stable. Necrosis doesn'tabclook to be spreading.
我说的是Foreman
I was talking about Foreman.
他真的要走吗?
is he really gonna leave?
这是人们被开除后的惯常做法
That's usually what peopleabcdo when they get fired.
你为什么拿我出气?abc我只是关心他有什么打算
Why are you biting my head off? I wasabcjust wondering what he was gonna do.
你说得对 对不起abc不是你的错
You're right. I'm sorry.abcIt's not your fault.
这也不是House的错
It's not house's fault either.
他给过你们机会 你们不要
He gave you guys a chance,you blew it.
他没有给我们机会abc他一来就发最后通牒
Uh, he didn't give us aabcchance,he gave us an ultimatum.
我本以为在这儿已经干了五年abc他会容许你犯一两个错
I would've thought five years hereabcwould buy a mistake or two.
救我!
Help me!
我无法呼吸!abc像是有东西压在我胸口上!
I can't breathe! Feels like something's on my chest!
像是心脏病发作
Looks like a heart attack.
我想你已经知道了
I assume you've heard.
我不能强迫他
I can't override him.
我不是让你强迫他
I'm not asking you to override him.
我想让你写封推荐信
I'm asking for aabcletter of recommendation.
Eric 现在的情况是...
Eric, the reality here is...
House有理由开除你
house should've fired you.
你伪造病历 置医院的名声不顾
You falsified medical records, putabcthis hospital's reputation in jeopardy.
你能保住执照已是万幸了
You're lucky you still have a license.
但没有推荐信 我无法在别处找到好工作
I can't get a decent position at anotherabchospital without a recommendation.
对不起
I'm sorry.
胸口的痛并非心绞痛abc心电图排除了心脏病发作
Chest pain wasn't angina.abcEkg ruled out heart attack.
那么 好消息是 没有心脏病发作
So the good news is, heabcdidn't have a heart attack.
坏消息是 我开除了唯一abc对心脏病有所了解的人
The bad news is,I apparently fired the only guyabcwho actually knows what a heart attack looks like.
这么说 这位不信上帝的上帝使者abc患上了不是心脏病的心脏病
So the man of god who doesn't believe inabcgod had a heart attack that isn't a heart attack.
谁敢说我挑病例不独具慧眼?
Do I know how toabcpick awesome cases or what?
可能是凝血紊乱
could be a clotting disorder.
三个不同症状abc三个部位有凝块?
Three differentabcsymptoms,three different clots?
我知道 这多酷啊
I know. How cool is that?
你们两个去做个血管造影
You two do an angio.
既然你无心工作abc何不去帮我买张彩票?
You don't want to work, so why don'tabcyou just go get me a lottery ticket?
他病得越厉害abc我就越是觉得运气来了
The sicker he gets,the luckier I feel.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
我还没向他作自我介绍呢
I've been wanting to introduce myself.
你真的是处男吗?
Are you really a virgin?
你只需医治我 无需相信我
You have to treat me. Youabcdon't have to believe me.
但治疗之前 我们先要进行诊断
And before we treat you,weabchave to diagnose you.
不知道你的话是否可信会造成阻碍
Not knowing whether we can believeabcyou is making that difficult.
我说的每句话都是真的
Everything I've told you is true.
你放弃你的信仰abc只因为一个孩子误会了?
You lost your faith becauseabca teenager got confused?
还因为教会抛弃了我abc我的上帝也遗弃了我
And the church abandonedabcme,and my god forsook me,
我想不到一个理由abc为什么上帝会这么做
and I couldn't come up withabca rson why god would do that.
上帝赋予教会和孩子以自由意志
god gave the churchabcand the kid free will.
他们行使自由意志 伤害了你
Their exercise of thatabcfree will hurt you.
也就是说 你是上帝赐予abc人类权力的的受害者
Means you're just a victimabcof god's gift to mankind.
是 上帝想要生活有意义abc无自由意志的生活没有意义
Oh, yeah. God wants life to have meaning.abcLife's meaningless without free will.
有自由意志 就得受苦abc所以上帝要我们受苦
With free will, there's alwaysabcsuffering. So god wants suffering.
还没讲完这些论辩 我就厌倦了
I got tired of that argumentabcbefore I even finished saying it.
就算我买账 上帝又做了什么?
And even if I bought that,abcwhat the hell is god doing?
大手笔的?
Just the big stuff?
上帝操控飓风 地震abc随意就杀死无数人
The acts of god, the hurricanes,the earthquakes,abcthe random killings of millions of innocent people.
我们就乖乖祈祷
Then we better damn pray.
天 真希望你没有恋童癖
God, I wish you weren'ta pedophile.
肺没问题 无栓塞 胸膜炎 肺炎
lungs are clean. No embolism.abcNo pleurisy, no pneumonia.
抱歉 这可能有点痛
I'm sorry. This is gonna hurt.
不痛
No, it's fine.
- 一点都不?abc- 不 怎么了?
- no pain at all?abc- No. Why?
你该感到痛的 这个呢?
Because there should be. You feel that?
没感觉
No.
局域性麻木是个新症状
Regional anesthesia is a new symptom.
除非胸痛和麻木有联系
Not if the chest painisabcrelated to the numbness.
这不是循环问题 是神经性的
It's not circulatory. It's neurological.
做个神经传导测试 另外小心
Run a nerve-conductionabcstudy. And be careful.
如果你杀了他 他会和恶魔共舞
If you kill him, he'llabcbe dancing with the dark one.
你为啥去掺和Cuddy孩子的取名礼?
why the hell are you goingabcto Cuddy's baby naming?
那是宗教礼节 很乏味的
It's a religious ceremony. It's boring.
干嘛不去喝得醉醺醺的然后自怨自艾?
Why waste a good evening that could be much betterabcspent in a drunken stupor feeling sorry for yourself?
- 好吧abc- 好吧? 好 你不去了?
- Okay.abc- Okay? Okay, you won't go?
好吧 你对Cuddy的真是尽职尽责
Okay, your obligation toabcCuddy is fulfilled.
你为什么这样做?
Why are you doing this?
为什么Hillary要征服珠峰?
Why did hillary conquer everest?
你总有理由 虽然很烂 但总是个理由
You always have a reason. It'sabcusually a bad one,but a reason.
她越来越孩子气
She's being childish.
看 这就是烂理由的典型
See, that's an example fromabcthe bad category.
是怨恨吗?
Is it resentment?
鹳衔回来新孩子 而你却不想分妈妈?
The stork brought home a new baby,abcand you don't want to share mommy?
还是你见不得别人高兴?
Or you just can'tabcstand to see others happy?
她就想玩我
She's trying to play me.
如果我让她成功 那恐怖分子就赢了
If I let her succeed,the terrorists win.
我听说急诊室会招人
I heard there mightabcbe an opening in the E.R.
Foreman是神经学家 他不会--
Foreman's a neurologist.That'sabcnot where he--
在Miami时 我在急诊室做过
I did an E.R.Rotation in miami.
如果我找到了另外的职位abc我想House会重新雇佣Foreman
If I can find another position, Iabcfigure house will rehire Foreman.
别放弃
Don't quit.
Cuddy不会给Foreman写推荐信
Cuddy wouldn't giveabcForeman a recommendation.
他没法找到满意的工作
He's not gonna be ableabcto find a decent job.
Foreman也不该走
Foreman shouldn't leave either.
你认为他们该分手?
You think they should split up?
办公室恋情本就不是好主意
Office romances are a bad idea.
我们这种是例外中的例外
We beat some very long odds.
哇 你还是把满腔感情留到婚礼吧
Wow, why don't you save theabcgushy stuff for the wedding?
House在玩你
House is playing with you.
如果你纵容他了 他将不再尊重你
If you let him get away with it,abche's not gonna respect you anyway.
或是在帮你 他知道这样下去没好结果
Or house is helping you. Heabcknows it probably won't work out.
他正好帮你个忙
And he's actually doing you a favor.
这可真像House的风格
Yeah, that sounds a lot more like house.
我知道Mercy要招人 我打个电话
I know they're looking for someoneabcat mercy. I'll make a call.
你上司总那样?
your boss always like that?
通常更糟 找到个同伴会让他好过些
Usually worse. Finding a fellowabcaeist always makes his day.
有没想过这是上帝在考验你的忠诚?
Think it's possible maybeabcgod's testing your faith?
我早没了
No, I already failed.
他这么做毫无意义
There'd be no point inabcwhat he's doing to me now.
找到了 像是肋间神经痛
Got something. Looksabclike inter costal neuralgia.
什么意思?
what's that?
有东西损伤了你的肋间神经
Something's traumatizing one of theabcnerves that runs along your ribs.
解释了胸痛及麻木 还有肌肉萎缩
Explains the chest pain and numbness.abcCould also cause muscle atrophy.
- 会影响眼睛吗?abc- 怎么了?
- Does it do anything to the eyes?abc- Wh what's wrong?
你又看见上帝了?
Are you seeing jesus again?
我什么都看不见 右眼好像瞎了
I'm seeing nothing.
眼科检查正常
ophthalmological exam's normal.
眼部结构没有问题
Nothing structurally wrong with the eye.
心率下降
his heart rate's down.
感觉丧失在扩散 肌肉进一步萎缩--abc他逐渐丧失机能
Sensory loss is becoming more diffuse,abcprogressive muscle weakness--he's shutting down.
应该是系统问题 像自身免疫性疾病
It's got to be somethingabcsystemic, like autoimmune.
脑脊液检测急性多发性神经根炎阴性
Csf was clear for guillain-barre.
癌症?
Cancer?
造影检查未见肿瘤
imaging studies haveabcbeen clear for tumors.
那就是感染
Then that leaves infection.
那样的话 白细胞数会飙升
He'd be brimming with white blood cells.
或许 我们是在杜兰音乐会后台出口
or we are at the back stageabcdoor of a duran duran concert.
周围有无数女生尖叫
Hundreds of screamingabcgirls clustered around.
这意味着什么?
What does that mean?
女孩们喜欢摇滚乐队
That girls like rock bands.
粉丝到场意味着乐队到场
The presence of the fansabcindicates the presence of the band.
不同的夜晚-- 同样的乐队 同样的门
Different night--abcsa band,same door.
但一个女粉丝都没有
Now there's not a girl in sight.
这是什么意思?
What does that mean?
抱歉 我不了解头发乐队
Sorry,I don't speak hair band.
不是头发乐队 是新浪漫乐队
They weren't a hair band.abcThey were new romantics.
乐队离开了?
The band already left?
没 乐队还在演出
Nope,the band's stillabcthere,still rocking out.
啥候粉丝缺席不表明乐队也缺席?
When does the absence of the fansabcnot indicate the absence of the band?
2009年
When it's 2009.
没多少杜兰杜兰迷了
There aren't any duran duran fans.
不再制造
They don't make them anymore.
没有感染 可以是粉丝没了abc即白细胞没了
If there's no infection,it's becauseabcthere aren't any fans,no white cells.
你是说脾?
You think his spleen?
我要想明说还干嘛用这么多隐喻?
Why do I bother with these greatabcmetaphors if I still have to spell it out?
是 就是脾
Yes,I think it's his spleen.
去做活检
Go get a biopsy.
我还得把"周一的新月"赶出脑海abc(Duran Duran乐队的名曲)
I'll try to get new moonabcon monday out of my head.
你为什么现在说话了?
Why are you talking this time?
如果我退出 你会重新雇用Foreman?
If I quit,will you rehire Foreman?
为什么?
Why?
他找不到别的工作
He can't find another job.
我能
I can.
你真要为他牺牲?
And you're willing toabcmake that sacrifice for him?
是
Yes.
Foreman知道吗?
Does Foreman know about this plan?
知道
Yes.
如果他都同意 我干嘛拒绝?
Well,if he's okay withabcit,who am I to say no?
别动
hold still.
你认为是脾的问题?
You think it's my spleen?
他们正在查
That's what they're testing.
如果我治好了你 接下来会发生什么?
So if I happen to cureabcyou,what happens then?
你会以为是上帝是借我手?
You start thinking thatabcgod was working through me?
有奇迹的成分?
This is some sort of miracle?
你以为我是傻子?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
正测试呢
That's what I'm testing.
失去信仰不是我选择的
Losing my faith wasn't a choice I made.
只是没了 没了也挺好
It happened. It's gone for good.
但如果它魔法般消失 也可能魔法般回来
but if it can magicallyabcdisappear,it can magically reappear,
这也是你想要的
and that's what you're hoping.
- 你的工作...abc- 垃圾
Your job...sucks.
我正想说
That's my point.
你调调奶泡咖啡 赚的钱都更多abc你却还在传播福音
You can make more money frapping decafs,andabcyet you're still ministering to the meek.
上帝都离去了 干嘛还帮他干活?
Why do the lord's work if theabclord has left the building?
我一生都呆在教堂里
I've been with theabcchurch my entire adult life.
这是我唯一能拿出手的技能
It's my only marketable skill.
我还能嗅到残存信仰的气味
I detect t stink of leftover faith.
你是说伪善 那你呢?
You want to talkabchypocrisy,what about you?
你表现得漠不关心 但却在拯救生命
You act like you don't care aboutabcanyone,but here you are saving lives.
解谜而已
Solving puzzles.
拯救生命是附带的
Saving lives is just collateral damage.
啊 真不错
Yeah,nice try.
我认为你不是想别人证明你对
I don't think you're lookingabcfor somebody to prove you right.
你在找人证明你错了 给你希望
I think you're looking for somebodyabcto prove you wrong,to give you hope.
你需要信念 不是吗?
You want to believe,don't you?
是 我想走出去然后发现abc自己身在妓女丛中
Yeah,I want to walk out and findabcmyself in a forest of whore trees,
但我不认为和水果私通是好主意
but I don't think it's a good idea toabctell people to go fornicate with fruit.
嘿 我刚说到你...
Hey,I was just talking about you...
谈到伪善和妓女 差不多等于你
not you specifically--whoresabcand hypocrisy.
你说得对
You were right.
我不想你去
I don't want you there.
那是充满爱和接纳的特殊时刻
It's a special occasion filledabcwith love and acceptance,
我最不想要的就是感到厌恶和轻蔑
and the last thing I need is someone thereabcwho's filled with loathing and contempt.
好吧
Okay.
就这样?
That's it?
你真不会来了?
You're really not coming?
我真不会来
I'm really not coming.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
上帝 我感到自己长大了
Gosh,I feel so grown up.
很明显他是在玩你 想看你是否认真
He's obviously just jerking youabcaround,wants to see if you're serious.
如果你坚持 我想他会让Foreman回来的
If you just stick it out,Iabcthink he'll bring Foreman back.
我不认为 也许我错了 我想你们该分手
I don't,and even if I'm wrong,Iabcthink you should still split up.
你俩发现对方床上有另一个女人abc只是时间问题
It's just a matter of time before one ofabcyou finds the other in bed with another woman.
这可真像是恋爱专家说的话
This coming from the relationship expert.
维持12年了 还在继续
12 years and counting.
嘿 如果你都能保持那么久 别人也能
Hey,if you can make it thatabclong,then anyone can.
好笑的是说维持关系很容易的俩人abc都是单身
Funny how the two people in the room whoabcthink relationships are easy are both single.
我不认为容易
I don't think they're easy.
这就是为何我说如果找到了好的abc就不应该放弃
That's why I think if you find somethingabcthat could be good,you should hang onto it.
任何事都有好的一面
Everything could be good.
不管多小
Very lite ever is.
脾没问题 只有些不起眼的细菌
His spleen is fine,justabcsome insignificant traces of minor bugs.
没有能致病的因素
Nothing that'd make him sick.
什么细菌?
Which minor bugs?
为何当人们有了孩子就突然信教了?
Why do people suddenlyabcfind religion when they have kids?
对未知的恐惧
Fear of the unknown.
信仰的基础
Cornerstone of faith.
这讲得通
I think it makes perfect sense.
因为讲不通所以讲得通
So it makes sense becauseabcit doesn't make sense.
事实上你为此困扰也讲不通
The fact that you're railing aboutabcit doesn't make a lot of sense.
你喜欢你老板 是吧?
You really got a thing for your boss,huh?
我喜欢她的那地方
I've got a thing for my boss's thing.
实际上...她那地方也没什么好
She doesn't have a thing...per se.
我喜欢隐喻
I'm big on metaphors.
你呢?
What about you?
29年单身生活
29 years of celibacy.
是什么让你犹豫不决?
What's holding you back now?
谁想和神父恋爱呢?
Who wants a relationship with a priest?
谁又想恋爱呢?
Who wants a relationship?
House?
是圣水
It's the holy water.
我们以为如果是感染abc一定是严重的
We assumed if it was an infection,itabchad to be something big and nasty.
但他有肺胞菌肺炎 这到处都存在的细菌abc本不会致病
But he has pneumocystis,a harmless bugabcthat's everywhere and never makes anyone sick,
除非免疫系统损坏了
unless they have aabccompromised immune system.
那神父尼采患有艾滋病
So father nietzsche has aids.
不可能
impossible.
我从没输过血
I've never had a blood transfusion.
没静脉注射毒品
I've never done I.V.Drugs.
没做过爱
I've never had sex.
那就证明看看 做个测试
So prove it. Have an aids test.
不
No.
我知道我没有艾滋病
I know I don't have aids.
我们要知道了是什么病 才能治疗
We can't treat you untilabcwe know what it is.
阴性结果什么都不能证明
A negative result proves nothing.
万一是假阳性abc我将永远失去别人对我最后的信任
On the off chance it's a false positive,Iabcpermanently loseany credibility I have left.
你刚刚已经失去了
I'd say you just lost that.
我早就失去你的信任了吧
I'd say I lost that withabcyou a long time ago.
我们得开始治疗艾滋
we should start treatment for aids.
要先确认才行
we need to be sure.
抗艾滋病药物会毁了他的心 肝和肾的
The antiretrovirals could fryabchis heart,his liver,his kidneys.
这个险我愿意冒
I'm willing to take that chance.
你太大胆了
Big of you.
我更担心那个被侵犯的小孩
I'm more worried aboutabcthe kid he molested.
我们应该找到他 让他接受检查
We should be findingabchim and getting him tested.
他很可能已经检查过了
You don't think he already got tested?
他也许已经检查了 可能还没有abc但我不愿冒这个险
Maybe he did,maybe he didn't,butabcthat's a chance I'm not willing to take.
依照法律 我们不能向abc患者的性伴侣告知性病检测结果
Legally,we can't informabcsexual partners about stds.
那不是什么久经江湖的老色鬼
This isn't some middle-agedabcbarfly who likes it bareback.
那只是个被侵犯的无辜的孩子
This is an innocent kid who was molested.
你只想让那个牧师再次名声扫地abc然后被调走
You just want to rub the priest'sabcface in it,get him transferred again.
天堂驱逐骗子 难道做错了
Yeah,heaven forbid aabcdiddler has job issues.
你会惹上官司
And you get brought upon charges.
这周我失去的医生够多了
I've lost enough doctors this week.
按艾滋病给予治疗
Treat him for aids.
我找到工作了
I found a job.
我不知道你有找工作
I didn't know you were looking.
Mercy医院的Eggers说周一就可以上班了
Eggers at mercy says I can start monday.
你为什么...
Why wouldabcyou--
House说如果我离开 你就可以回来
house says if I go,you can come back.
现在还不到两天
It's been less than two days.
你这么快就对我失望了?
Give up on me that fast?
竟然背着我偷偷找工作?
You get a job behind my back?
你似乎觉得我骗了你
You're acting like I'm cheating on you.
我说过我会处理的
I said I would handle this.
House早就知道你会这么想
House knew you'd be like this.
我也觉得House比你更了解我
I guess house knowsabcme better than you do.
没有做两手准备真是太笨了
Too bad I don't go both ways.
晚安
Good night.
我真讨厌他们把蘑菇放在芝士下面
Don't you hate when they put theabcmushrooms underneath the cheese?
你出席只是助纣为虐
Your attendance isabcvalidating her hypocrisy.
如果她邀请你参加宗教私刑礼abc你也会去吗?
If she invited you to aabcceremonial lynching,would you go?
那就要看她准备了什么美食
It would depend on what she was serving.
所有人都是伪君子
Everyone's a hypocrite.
为何你就揪着Cuddy这一点不放呢?
Why are you suddenly so obsessed withabcCuddy's particular brand?
只是找点话题
Just making conversation.
你更想讨论蘑菇和芝士吗
Would you rather we go back toabctalking about mushrooms and cheese?
你才是伪君子
You're the hypocrite!
你想去
You want to go!
你也不讨厌那个孩子
You don't resent this baby.
你想参加
You want to be a part of it.
是的 除非她已经16岁...在某些州
Yes,but not until her 16thabcbirthday...in some states.
太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
你们俩太般配了
You two deserve each other.
想去就去吧 然后表现得像样些
If you want to go,just goabcand act like a human being.
哇 除了两点 你的建议妙极了
Wow,solid advice,except for two things.
我装得好像一点也不想去abc因为我真的不想去 还有...
I'm acting like I don't want to goabcbecause I don't want to go,and...
我真的不能装得像个人样
I am incapable ofabcacting like a human being.
Ryan?
是我
Yeah.
我是Chris Taub医生
I'm dr. Chris taub.
能谈谈吗?
Can we talk?
可以
Yeah.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
能私下谈谈么?
Uh,in private?
这里应该没人留意我们
Nobody's listening to us here.
我在普林斯顿医院工作
Um,I work at princetonabcplainsboro hospital.
有些事是关于Daniel Bresson神父
I have some news aboutabcfather daniel bresson.
他出什么事了?
What about him?
我们认为他得了艾滋病
Uh,we believe he has aids.
哦 然后呢?
Okay,so?
嗯 考虑到四年前的那件事
Well...uh,given theabcincident four years ago,
我觉得你最好也检查一下abc除非你已经检查过了
I think you should be tested,unlessabcyou've already done so.
他的病情如何?
How sick is he?
非常严重
Very.
好的 谢谢你
Okay. Well,um,thanks.
你检查过了吗?
Have you been tested?
嗯
Uh,yeah.
还有呢?
And?
这和你没有任何关系吧
And it really isn't anyvof your business.
我想要回我的工作
I want my job back.
爱情 牺牲 欺骗 然后是背叛
Love,sacrifice,deception,andabcnow betrayal.
这比肥皂剧好看多了
This is better than a telenovela.
怎么了?
What going on?
那好...除非 Foreman来找我abc是你们商量好的
Well...either Foreman isabchere,as the two of you discussed,
他求我把工作还他abc而你被辞退作为交换
to beg for his job back inabcexchange for me dumping you,
不然... 没事
or...nothing.
你想让我丢了工作?
You're trying to get me fired?
我想不如你辞职 我留下 这是你昨晚提议的啊
I'm suggesting you quit and I stay,whichabcis exactly what you suggested last night.
我已经告诉Eggers我不要那份工作了
I told eggers I didn't want the job.
再找一份
Find another one.
你只花了8小时就找到那份工作了
Only took you eightabchours to find that one.
重点是 为什么你不告诉我你要这么做?
The point is,why didn't youabctell me you were doing this?
为什么你自己过来了?
Why are you here without me?
你太敏感了
You're overreacting.
我们迟点再谈
We'll talk about this later.
现在就在谈这件事
Oh,that's what this is about.
你在操纵一切
It's about you taking control.
你接受不了我来拯救你
It's about you not being able toabchandle me saving your ass.
你现在不也想控制一切?
And you're not beingabccontrolling right now?
哇
yeah!
现在谁占上风了啊?
Who's the controlling bitch now?
House 住嘴
House,shut up.
你从没想过要接受那个工作
You never wanted to take that other job.
你从没想过要帮我
You never wanted to save me.
你假装想帮我abc这样你就不会感到愧疚
You wanted to offer to saveabcme so you wouldn't feel guilty.
你早知道我会拒绝
You knew I'd say no.
所以你现在这么生气
That's why you're so mad right now.
你这笨蛋
You're an idiot.
好了 你可以跟她走 然后收拾东西滚蛋
Well,either you can go after herabcand try and patch things up,
你也可以甩了她 然后复职
or you blow her off andabctake your old job back.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
抗艾滋治疗不见效
Aids meds aren't gonna work.
如果你同意做检查 我们可以停止治疗abc或者你可以说真话
If you'd let us do a test,we could stopabctreating you,or you could stop lying.
我有过这种感觉
I know the feeling.
血压上升
Bp's climbing.
你还好吗?
You feeling okay?
不 我觉得好热
No,I feel flushed.
整个人像着火一样
Ah,I'm burning all over.
噢 胸口
Ah,my chest.
这不是个新的症状
it's not a new symptom.
只是对艾滋病治疗的反应而已
It's just a reaction to the aids meds.
病情恶化了
He reacted by getting worse.
意味着这不是艾滋病
Means it's not aids.
"撒旦从耶和华面前退去abc击打约伯 使他长满毒疮 (圣经"约伯记")
So went satan forth from the presence ofabcthe lord and smote job sore with boils.
你认为是高IgE综合症?
You think it's hyper-ige syndrome?
我喜欢它的俗名"约伯综合症"
I prefer the colloquialabcterm "job syndrome."
对应症状和我的引文
Explains the symptoms and my quote.
我们一开始就查过了
That's the first thing I checked.
IgE抗体正常
Ige levels are normal.
可能是其它遗传疾病
Could be some other genetic disorder.
脑部的微小肿瘤可以解释失明和幻觉
Cerebral microtumors could explainabcthe blindness and the hallucinations.
我们找不到肿瘤
We didn't find any tumors.
所以我说的不是"肿瘤"
That's why I didn't say "tumors."
而是"微小肿瘤"
I said "microtumors."
那么说你的解释是基于abc我们只是普通白痴 还没蠢到家?
So your explanation doesn't dependabcon us being major morons,just morons?
我们应该做个基因检测
We should start genetic testing.
耗时太长了
It takes too long.
那直接开始治疗
So we start treatment.
治疗就是动手术
Treatment is surgery.
没确诊前我们不能给他开刀
We can't open him upabcwithout confirmation.
那你的立场是 不检测也不治疗?
So your position is weabccan't test and we can't treat?
我的立场是你错了
My position is you're wrong.
这样下去不行
This isn't gonna work.
你没开玩笑吧?
Are you kidding?
气氛前所未有地活跃
I've never felt more alive.
冲突才能迸发创意
Conflict breeds creativity.
去做基因检测
Go run the genetic tests.
收到
On it.
现在你们认为不是艾滋病了?
So now you don't think I have aids?
我还是认为是艾滋病
I still think it's aids.
但以防万一abc我们要寻找别的可能性
On the off chance it isn't,we'reabcpursuing other avenues.
Ryan
Ryan.
他...快死了吗?
He's,um...he's dying?
我们不知他得了什么病
Uh,we don't know what's wrong with him.
我能和他说几句吗?
Can I speak to him?
我想这不太适合
I don't think that's a good idea.
Ryan?
你跟我--
um,why don't I get you--
别 Ryan 这不是适当的时--
come on,ryan,now'sabcnot a good ti--
对不起...
I'm sorry...
为所有的事
for everything.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我知道 没事了
I know. I know.
重新考虑Cuddy的事了么?
Any second thoughts about Cuddy?
没
Nope.
但欢迎你发表高见
But please,feel free to blather on.
她害怕要独自抚养孩子
Raising a child on her own is scary.
她所做的 与你 与所有人无异--abc为了逃避痛苦
She's just doing what you do,whatabceveryone does-- trying to avoid pain.
宗教不是人民的鸦片abc(引马克思)
Religion is not the opiate of the masses.
宗教只是人民的安慰剂
Religion is the placeboof the masses.
如果你想说的是她并不虚伪--
If you're saying she'sabcnot a hypocrite--
我没有
I'm not.
我只是想你理性地思考她的行为
I'm trying to give you a rationalabcreason to overlook her hypocrisy
就不会觉得参加仪式虚伪了
so you don't feel likeabca hypocrite for going.
对不起
Oh,sorry.
继续
Continue.
即使世上存在绝对的真理abc我们也无法得悉其全部
Okay,even if an absolute truthabcexists,we can't know all of it,
你不能因Cuddy承认这点而苛责她
and you can't condemnabcher for recognizing that.
你在排除症状?
Are you eliminating symptoms?
我们无法得知一切
We can know everything.
这是医学 不是形而上学
This is medicine not metaphysics.
真理就是真理
Truth is truth.
这下符合了
It fits.
这不符合
It doesn't fit.
你不能排除症状
You can't eliminate a symptom.
如果不是症状就可以
I can if it's nota symptom.
那是什么
Well,what is it?
不是症状
Not a symptom.
你不会死
You're not gonna die.
你患了Wiskott-Aldrich综合症abc(湿疹血小板减少伴免疫缺陷综合症)
You have wiskott-aldrich syndrome.
它会削弱你的免疫系统abc使你出现所有艾滋病的症状
It impairs your immune system,makes you susceptible toabcall the aids stuff without actually having aids.
不是后天染上的
And you didn't catch it.
是与生俱来的
You were born with it.
上帝的又一件礼物
Another gift from god.
你确定?
You sure?
基因检测可以确定 但它解释了所有症状--abc脚趾脱落 胸痛 失明 皮疹
Genetic test should confirm it,but it explainsabcall your symptoms-- toe,chest,eyes,skin.
那我的幻觉呢?
What about my hallucination?
因为苏格兰威士忌
Scotch explains that.
那么说 只是一个巧合
But that was just a coincidence.
巧合时有发生
Coincidences do happen.
但一开始 是这个巧合把我带到了医院
That coincidence is what brought meabcto you in the first place.
你答应你不会归功于上帝
You promised you wouldn't go there.
爱因斯坦说: "巧合是abc上帝匿名出现的方式"
Einstein said,"coincidence isabcgod's way of remaining anonymous."
有个佛州的女人说: "看呐abc耶稣在我的芝士三文治上"
A woman in florida said,"look,jesus isabcon my cheese sandwich."
你开始不想接这个病例
You didn't even want to take my case.
你根本不认为我有病
You didn't even think I was sick.
我错了 并不能证实上帝存在
The fact that I was wrongabcis not a proof of god.
我只是想弄明白abc我的生命怎么会在一天逆转?
I'm just trying to understand how my lifeabccould completely turn around in a single day.
别担心
Don't worry.
你的生命很快会像以前那样糟糕
Your life will go backabcto sucking soon enough.
发生在你身上的一切abc都能得到合理解释
Everything that happened toabcyou can be rationally explained.
我知道
I know.
只是...
It's just...
有太多的巧合了
that's a lot of coincidences.
House对那个牧师的诊断是对的
House was right about the priest.
基因检测证实是Wiskott-Aldrich
Genetic test confirmed itabcwas wiskott-aldrich.
而我差点就让他出院了
And I would've discharged him.
所有人都会让他出院 包括House
Everybody would've dischargedabchim,house included.
他开始只是用这个病例拖延时间
He only took that case as a stall.
不管怎样 这是个真正的病例abc而且他解决了
And yet it was a realabccase,and he solved it.
但他破坏了自己的原则abc故意忽略已确定的症状
But by violating his own principlesabcand ignoring the admitting symptoms.
尽管他找到了病因
Still he somehow got away with it.
挽救了另一条生命
Saved another life.
你希望他今晚出现
You want him there tonight.
你应该告诉他
You should tell him.
外面-- 很冷呢
It's--it'sabccold out there.
至少你还有双鞋子盖住脚趾头
At least you haveabcshoes that cover your toes.
定在今晚了?
So it's tonight?
没错
Yep.
天公不作美
Bad weather for it,hu
也许这是你的运气
maybe you'll get lucky.
没准你姐姐觉得这种天气开车太危险abc就不来了
Maybe your sister will decide theabcroads are too dangerous to drive on.
承你贵言
Fingers crossed.
玩得开心
Have fun.
"Cuddy 小夜曲" 大叔谱曲
"Cuddy Serenade"